A Guide to the Richmond Symphony Archives, 1965-1982
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
Richmond Symphony Archives, 1965-1982
Special Collections and Archives, James Branch Cabell Library, Virginia Commonwealth University
M 257
22 linear feet and scrapbooks
Richmond Symphony
Administrative Information
Access
Access to Series I must by granted in writing by the Executive Director of the Richmond Symphony.
Acquisition Information
Donated by The Board of the Richmond Symphony 10 March 1994.
Biographical/Historical Information
Virginia's capital had its own symphony orchestra for a brief period in the 1930's; but the present Richmond Symphony dates from 1956, when it was founded as a community orchestra. Edgar Schenkman led the orchestra as its music director and conductor from its founding until 1971, when direction was taken over by French conductor Jacques Houtmann. The Symphony expanded greatly during Houtmann's sixteen years of leadership, achieving regional orchestra status and turning its part-time "Little Symphony" into a full-time Sinfonia in 1973. The first such professional symphonic ensemble to be established in Virginia, the Richmond Sinfonia proceeded to expand its schedule, particularly in the area of in-school concerts for Virginia's school children. Further performing flexibility was lent by the Symphony's String, Brass, and Woodwind Ensembles. The development of student concerts and the sponsorship of youth orchestras rounded out the Symphony's extensive involvement with music education in the state.
In 1987 the orchestra welcomed its third director, the young George Manahan from the New Jersey Symphony Orchestra. The Richmond Symphony continues to be the largest performing arts organization in Virginia. Concert series, both classical and popular, are held in the Richmond Mosque and the Virginia Center for the Performing Arts (Carpenter Center), a downtown theater in whose renovation the Symphony took part. These and other special performances are supported by foundations, private donations, and grants from the National Endowment for the Arts and the Virginia Commission for the Arts.
The Symphony's season runs approximately from October to April.
Scope and Content Information
The collection consists of correspondence, contracts, and publicity materials, chiefly from the 1970's. Most of the material focuses on the artistic and financial arrangements made for each season's performances, though considerable attention is also given to special programs, public relations, and fundraising activities. Individual files detail the association with the Symphony of both members and guest artists. These may include personal data as well as professional details.
Arrangement
Arrangement
The materials are arranged alphabetically within each series except Correspondence, which is arranged first chronologically and then alphabetically.
Organization
Series I--Personnel (1969-1981) Subseries: Musicians, Guest Artists, Staff, Applicants for Positions
Series II--Concerts (1973-1981)
Series III--Programs/Brochures (1962-1980)
Series IV--Planning/Operations (1965-1982)
Series V--Correspondence (1973-1982)
Series VI--Oversized Materials (1980) Located in oversize area.
Contents List
- Personnel 1969-1981
  - Musicians
    - Abbott, Kenneth: French Horn 1974 (Box-folder 1.1)
    - Ager, Kris: Violin, n.d. (Box-folder 1.2)
    - Allan, Betty: Cello 1974 (Box-folder 1.3)
    - Aunins, Edgar: French Horn 1974-1976 (Box-folder 1.4)
    - Baedk, Ronald: Trombone 1981 (Box-folder 1.5)
    - Bahler, Peter: Bass 1974-1979 (Box-folder 1.6)
    - Baker, Rita May: Cello 1971-1975 (Box-folder 1.7)
    - Bakker, Anne: Cello 1973-1978 (Box-folder 1.8)
    - Bambakidis, Peter, Violin 1973-1979 (Box-folder 1.9)
    - Barker, Robert: Clarinet 1971-1978 (Box-folder 1.10)
    - Barnet, Lori: Cello 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1.11)
    - Benson, Jane: Piano 1980 (Box-folder 1.12)
    - Birkedahl, Walter: Bass 1976-1977 (Box-folder 1.13)
    - Bly, Car: French Horn/Conductor 1976 (Box-folder 1.14)
    - Bly, Randi Jean: Flute 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1.15)
    - Bradford, Larry: Violin 1973 (Box-folder 1.16)
    - Carver, Roger: French Horn 1975 (Box-folder 1.17)
    - Catchings, John: Cello 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1.18)
    - Cheatham, Peggy: Violin 1974 (Box-folder 1.19)
    - Colbert, John: Clarinet 1978-1979 (Box-folder 1.20)
    - Connelly, Mary Lou: Cello 1971-1977 (Box-folder 1.21)
    - Consiglio, Sandy: Oboe 1979 (Box-folder 1.22)
    - Cramer, Ernest: Violin 1975-1980 (Box-folder 1.23)
    - Cramer, Jennifer: Violin 1973-1975 (Box-folder 1.24)
    - Crump, Marilyn: Violin 1981 (Box-folder 1.25)
    - Cummings, Owen: Bass 1975-1976 (Box-folder 1.26)
    - Curry, William: Assistant Conductor 1975-1977 (Box-folder 1.27)
    - Denda, Nancy: Bass 1979-1981 (Box-folder 1.28)
    - Dorsam, Paul: Trumpet 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1.29)
    - Eastman, Nina Louise: Cello 1974-1975 (Box-folder 1.30)
    - Ellin, Vincent: Bassoon 1973-1974 (Box-folder 1.31)
    - Fardjad, Farid: Violin 1980 (Box-folder 1.32)
    - Farrar, John: Viola 1978-1980 (Box-folder 1.33)
    - Finkelstein, Paul: Cello 1978-1981 (Box-folder 1.34)
    - Floyd, John: Percussion 1973-1976 (Box-folder 1.35)
    - Formaini, Robert: Bass Trombone 1975-1977 (Box-folder 1.36)
    - Freedland, Debra: Oboe 1977-1978 (Box-folder 1.37)
    - Friedman, Jonathan: Bassoon 1981 (Box-folder 1.38)
    - Gagne, Alphonse: Clarinet/Bass 1972 (Box-folder 2.1)
    - Giacobbe, Carolyn: Violin 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2.2)
    - Golding, Kathleen: Oboe/English Horn 1978-1979 (Box-folder 2.3)
    - Greene, Kenneth: Viola 1974-1977 (Box-folder 2.4)
    - Grosjean, Richard James: Viola 1974 (Box-folder 2.5)
    - Gutman, Leonid: Viola 1975-1976 (Box-folder 2.6)
    - Handy, D. Antoinette: Flute 1976 (Box-folder 2.7)
    - Harding, Marian: Harp 1974 (Box-folder 2.8)
    - Hemmingway, Todd: Cello 1973-1979 (Box-folder 2.9)
    - Hoffheins, Richard: French Horn 1978 (Box-folder 2.10)
    - Houtmann, Jacques: Conductor 1976 (Box-folder 2.11)
    - Howard, Keith: Violin 1974 (Box-folder 2.12)
    - Johnson, Nancy: Violin 1981 (Box-folder 2.13)
    - Jones, Mary: Harp 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2.14)
    - Joy, Lisa: Violin 1977 (Box-folder 2.15)
    - Kelly, Kevin: Violin, n.d. (Box-folder 2.16)
    - Kiddler, Timothy, Violin 1976 (Box-folder 2.17)
    - Knopp, Stephen: French Horn 1971 (Box-folder 2.18)
    - Knudsvig, Peter: Trumpet 1974-1975 (Box-folder 2.19)
    - Kuhn, Milford: Horn 1974 (Box-folder 2.20)
    - Laird, Richard: Double Bass 1976-1979 (Box-folder 2.21)
    - Lamprey, Mark: Violin 1973-1976 (Box-folder 2.22)
    - Lasson, Stephanie: Violin 1973-1975 (Box-folder 2.23)
    - Lee, Fulton Jr.: Trumpet 1974 (Box-folder 2.24)
    - Lewis, Jungshin: Cello 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2.25)
    - Link, Robert Jr.: String Bass 1971-1974 (Box-folder 2.26)
    - Liscio, Henry: Violin 1974-1977 (Box-folder 2.27)
    - Mann, Adrian: Double Bass 1971 (Box-folder 2.28)
    - Mann, Leslie J.: Viola 1975 (Box-folder 2.29)
    - Marcellus, Mandy: Flute/Piccolo 1977 (Box-folder 2.30)
    - Masters, Michael: Cello 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2.31)
    - Mazur, Elizabeth: French Horn 1978-1979 (Box-folder 2.32)
    - McCurdy, Everett: Trumpet 1973 (Box-folder 33)
    - McKee, Robin: Flute/Piccolo 1976 (Box-folder 2.34)
    - Midney, Barbara: Oboe/English Horn 1977-1978 (Box-folder 2.35)
    - Migdal, Ann: Oboe 1976-1980 (Box-folder 2.36)
    - Mitchell, Sharon: Violin 1975-1979 (Box-folder 2.37)
    - Montoni, Raymond: Viola 1973-1975 (Box-folder 2.38)
    - Morgan, Michael: Bass 1973-1974 (Box-folder 2.39)
    - Mott, Jonathan: Violin/Bassoon 1976 (Box-folder 2.40)
    - Moulton, Kenneth: Trumpet 1974 (Box-folder 2.41)
    - Myers, Shirley: Viola 1976 (Box-folder 2.42)
    - O'bannon, John: Oboe 1973-1976 (Box-folder 2.43)
    - Pancarowicz, Raymond: Violin 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3.1)
    - Paterson, Alan: Horn 1980 (Box-folder 3.2)
    - Pates, Jacqueline: Harp 1969-1976 (Box-folder 3.3)
    - Patterson, Stephanie: Bass 1975-1979 (Box-folder 3.4)
    - Pereira, Paulo Sergio: Violin 1978 (Box-folder 3.5)
    - Perry, Virginia: Viola 1977 (Box-folder 3.6)
    - Pistolesi, Elizabeth: Violin 1973 (Box-folder 3.7)
    - Rogers, Laurel 1977-1979 (Box-folder 3.8)
    - Romaine, David: Cello 1970-1975 (Box-folder 3.9)
    - Rosato, Peter: Viola 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3.10)
    - Sasson, Carol: Viola 1974-1979 (Box-folder 3.11)
    - Schenkman, Edgar: Music Director/Conductor 1970-1973 (Box-folder 3.12)
    - Schuster, Savely: Cello 1975-1977 (Box-folder 3.13)
    - Shapiro, Barry: Viola 1976-1977 (Box-folder 3.14)
    - Shaw, Belinda: Bass 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3.15)
    - Soo Hoo, Peter: Viola 1981 (Box-folder 3.16)
    - Stern, Adele: Violin 1973 (Box-folder 3.17)
    - Stokes, Adde Bakker 1981 (Box-folder 3.18)
    - Switzer, Matthew: Cello 1977-1980 (Box-folder 3.19)
    - Takada, Miohisa: Violin 1971-1975 (Box-folder 3.20)
    - Toth, Kirk: Violin 1976 (Box-folder 3.21)
    - Tulchinsky, Alexander: Viola 1978-1981 (Box-folder 3.22)
    - Uitvlucht, Peter: English Horn 1973-1977 (Box-folder 3.23)
    - Umstead, Alan 1978 (Box-folder 3.24)
    - Van Valkenberg, Carl W.: Viola 1976-1978 (Box-folder 3.25)
    - Vaught, Kathleen: French Horn 1976-1979 (Box-folder 3.26)
    - Ward, R. D.: Trombone 1975-1981 (Box-folder 3.27)
    - Waters, Robert: Bass 1978 (Box-folder 3.28)
    - Watson, Richard: Assistant Conductor 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3.29)
    - Weil, Celia Moulyn: Violin 1974-1977 (Box-folder 3.30)
    - Weiler, Roger: Violin 1976 (Box-folder 3.31)
    - Weinreb, Alice: Flute/Piccolo 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3.32)
    - Wendt, Virginia: Cello 1973-1980 (Box-folder 3.33)
    - Wilhjelm, Cheryl: Oboe 1974 (Box-folder 3.34)
    - Wihjelm, C Christain: French Horn 1973-1976 (Box-folder 3.35)
    - Will, Christopher: Violin 1977 (Box-folder 3.36)
    - Willett, Van 1977 (Box-folder 3.37)
    - Williams, Delbert: Bass 1971-1980 (Box-folder 3.38)
    - Wing, Daniel: Viola 1975-1978 (Box-folder 3.39)
    - Womack, Sarah: Violin 1973 (Box-folder 3.40)
    - Zaret, Coralie: Violin 1977 (Box-folder 3.41)
  - Guest Artists
    - Ashkenazy, Vladimar: Piano 1979 (Box-folder 4.1)
    - Ashkenazy, Vladimar: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.2)
    - Atkins, Chet: Guitar 1975 (Box-folder 4.3)
    - Ax, Emanuel: Piano 1979 (Box-folder 4.4)
    - Ax, Emanuel: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.5)
    - Becker, Richard: Piano 1980 (Box-folder 4.6)
    - Bonell, Carlos: Guitar 1979 (Box-folder 4.7)
    - Bonell, Carlos: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.8)
    - Ciccolini, Aldo: Piano 1981 (Box-folder 4.9)
    - de Larrocha, Alicia: Piano 1981 (Box-folder 4.10)
    - Duphil, Monique: Piano 1979 (Box-folder 4.11)
    - Duphil, Monique: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.12)
    - Farley, Carole: Vocal 1978 (Box-folder 4.13)
    - Feit, Pierre: Oboe 1979 (Box-folder 4.14)
    - Feit, Pierre: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.15)
    - Ferrante and Teicher: Piano 1979 (Box-folder 4.16)
    - Ferrante and Teicher: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 4.17)
    - Fiedler, Arthur: Publicity File 1978 (Box-folder 4.18)
    - Fried, Miriam: Violin 1973-1974 (Box-folder 4.19)
    - Fried, Miriam: Violin 1976 (Box-folder 4.20)
    - Gubrud, Irene: Vocal 1980 (Box-folder 5.1)
    - Hellwig, Klaus: Piano 1976 (Box-folder 5.2)
    - Jones, Jack 1978 (Box-folder 5.3)
    - Kavafian, Ani: Violin 1979 (Box-folder 5.4)
    - Kavafian, Ani: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 5.5)
    - Kipnis, Igor: Harpsichord 1981 (Box-folder 5.6)
    - Knight, Eric: Conductor 1979 (Box-folder 5.7)
    - Knight, Eric: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 5.8)
    - Kraus, Lili: Piano 1973-1974 (Box-folder 5.9)
    - Kraus, Lili: Piano 1975 (Box-folder 5.10)
    - Lawrence, Carol: Vocal 1978 (Box-folder 5.11)
    - Lawrence, Carol: Publicity File 1978 (Box-folder 5.12)
    - Luca, Sergiu: Violin 1975 (Box-folder 5.13)
    - Luca, Sergiu: Violin 1980 (Box-folder 5.14)
    - Ma, Yo Yo: Cello 1980 (Box-folder 5.15)
    - Markova, Juliana: Piano 1978 (Box-folder 5.16)
    - McMurran, Cary: Piano 1975 (Box-folder 5.17)
    - Mintz, Shlomo: Violin 1978 (Box-folder 5.18)
    - Mints, Shlomo: Publicity File 1978 (Box-folder 5.19)
    - Myers, Jacquelyn Bartlett: Harp 1974 (Box-folder 5.20)
    - Parker, Louise: Vocal 1973-1974 (Box-folder 6.1)
    - Pennario, Leonard: Piano 1974 (Box-folder 6.2)
    - Phillips, Daniel: Violin 1981 (Box-folder 5.3)
    - Premezzi, Renato: Piano 1974 (Box-folder 6.4)
    - Rampal, Jean-Pierre: Flute 1981 (Box-folder 6.5)
    - Ringeisen, Bernard: piano 1975 (Box-folder 6.6)
    - Roge, Pascal: Piano 1974 (Box-folder 6.7)
    - The Romeros: Guitar Quartet 1975 (Box-folder 6.8)
    - Rosand, Aaron: Violin 1973-19
    - Rose, Leonard: Cello 1976 (Box-folder 6.10)
    - Shuttleworth, Barbara: Soprano 1975 (Box-folder 6.11)
    - Stern, Issac: Violin 1979 (Box-folder 6.12)
    - Stern, Issac: Publicity File 1978 (Box-folder 6.13)
    - Tacchino, Gabriel: Piano 1973 (Box-folder 6.14)
    - Thomas, Ronald B.: Cello 1980 (Box-folder 6.15)
    - Walker, Sandra: Vocal 1979 (Box-folder 6.16)
    - Watts, Andre: Piano 1975 (Box-folder 6.17)
    - Westcott, Mark: Piano 1976 (Box-folder 6.18)
    - Wilson, Nancy: Vocal 1979 (Box-folder 6.19)
    - Wilson, Nancy: Publicity File 1979 (Box-folder 6.20)
    - Zuckerman, Pinchas: Violin 1979 (Box-folder 6.21)
  - Staff
    - Adams, Cheryl: Office 1980 (Box-folder 7.1)
    - Christmann, Thomas: Director 1979-1981 (Box-folder 7.2)
    - Cox, Fred: Secretary, Board of Directors 1974 (Box-folder 7.3)
    - Darling, Suzanne: Office 1979 (Box-folder 7.4)
    - Director of Audience Development Applications 1980 (Box-folder 7.5)
    - Feuss, Patricia: Receptionist/Secretary 1978 (Box-folder 7.6)
    - General Manager Application 1980 (Box-folder 7.7)
    - Goode, Shelley: Office Intern 1979 (Box-folder 7.8)
    - Lambert, Charles: Accountant 1970-1972 (Box-folder 7.9)
    - Manager's Assistant Applications 1975-1980 (Box-folder 7.10)
    - Marketing Applications 1981 (Box-folder 7.11)
    - Staff Assistant Applications 1979 (Box-folder 7.12)
    - Warner, Carol: Accountant 1973-1974 (Box-folder 7.13)
  - Applicants for Positions
    - Applicants for Symphony: Assistant Conductor 1978-1980 (Box-folder 8.1)
    - Applicants for Symphony: Conductor 1974 (Box-folder 8.2)
    - Applicants for Symphony: Flute/Violin/Viola/Cello 1978 (Box-folder 8.3)
    - Applicants for Symphony: French Horn 1978 (Box-folder 8.4)
    - Applicants for Symphony: Oboe/English Horn 1978 (Box-folder 8.5)
    - Applicants of Symphony: Violin 1979 (Box-folder 8.6)
    - Bick, Donald 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8.7)
    - Ellis, Charles 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8.8)
    - Krajewski, Michael 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8.9)
    - Nafziger, Kenneth 1979-1980 (Box-folder 9.10)
    - Newell, Douglas 1979-1980 (Box-folder 4.11)
    - Vekshtein, Seymon 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8.12)
    - White, Joseph P. 1979-1980 (Box-folder 8.13)
- Concerts 1973-1981
  - All College Chorus 1979 (Box-folder 9.1)
  - American Cancer Society Concert 1977-1978 (Box-folder 9.2)
  - American Pops Festival 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9.3)
  - American Pops Festival: Steve Bassett 1980 (Box-folder 9.4)
  - American Pops Festival: Charlie Byrd 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9.5)
  - American Pops Festival: Cab Calloway 1981 (Box-folder 9.6)
  - American Pops Festival: William Curry 1978 (Box-folder 9.7)
  - American Pops Festival: Arthur Fiedler 1977-1978 (Box-folder 9.8)
  - American Pops Festival: Gilbert and Sullivan 1980 (Box-folder 9.9)
  - American Pops Festival Benny Goodman 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9.10)
  - American Pops Festival: Kingston Trio 1981 (Box-folder 9.11)
  - Ameriacan Pops Festival: Henry Mancini 1980 (Box-folder 9.12)
  - American Pops Festival: Ethel Meman 1980 (Box-folder 9.13)
  - American Pops Festival: Mitch Miller 1980 (Box-folder 9.14)
  - American Pops Festival: Mitch Miller 1981 (Box-folder 9.15)
  - American Pops Festival: Della Reese 1981 (Box-folder 9.16)
  - American Pops Festival: Doc Severinsen 1981 (Box-folder 9.17)
  - American Pops Festival: Bily Taylor Trio 1980 (Box-folder 9.18)
  - American Pops Festival: Sarah Vaughan 1976-1977 (Box-folder 9.19)
  - American Pops Festival: Sarah Vaughan 1979 (Box-folder 9.20)
  - Bach Mass: Richmond Symphony Chorus 1980-1981 (Box-folder 9.21)
  - Steve Bassett Benefit Concert 1977 (Box-folder 9.22)
  - Bicentennial Program 1974-1976 (Box-folder 9.23)
  - Bluefield College Concert 1973-1974 (Box-folder 9.24)
  - Brass Quintet, Summer 1983 (Box-folder 9a.1)
  - Brass Quintet 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9a.2)
  - Brass Quintet 1982-1983 (Box-folder 9a.3)
  - Brass Quintet: Ash Lawn, Charlottesville, Va. 1982 (Box-folder 9a.4)
  - Brass Quintet: Virginia Highlands Festival 1982 (Box-folder 9a.5)
  - Brass Quintet: VEPCO 1982 (Box-folder 9a.6)
  - Brass Quintet: Waynesboro, Va 1982 (Box-folder 9a.7)
  - Brookfield 1983 (Box-folder 9a.8)
  - Byrd Airport: Woodwind Quintet 1977 (Box-folder 9a.9)
  - Camp Memorial Theatre 1973-1974 (Box-folder 9a.10)
  - Central Fidelity Bank Pops: Peter Nero 1980 (Box-folder 10.1)
  - Central National Bank Pops Concert 1976 (Box-folder 10.2)
  - CNB Pops Concert: Chet Atkins 1975 (Box-folder 10.3)
  - CNB Pops Concert: Jose Feliciano 1976 (Box-folder 10.4)
  - CNB Pops Concert: Melba Moore 1977 (Box-folder 10.5)
  - Central State Hospital 1979 (Box-folder 10.6)
  - Chesterfield County School Concerts 1974 (Box-folder 10.7)
  - Chesterfield County School Concerts 1975-1976 (Box-folder 10.8)
  - Chesterfield County School Concerts 1976-1977 (Box-folder 10.9)
  - Chesterfield County School Concerts 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.10)
  - Colonial Heights High School Concert 1974-1975 (Box-folder 10.11)
  - Columbia Artists Community Concert Series 1974-1978 (Box-folder 10.12)
  - Commonwealth Woman's Club: Brass Quintet 1978 (Box-folder 10.13)
  - The Consul: Cancelled Project 1975-1976 (Box-folder 10.14)
  - Cosi Fan Tutte 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.15)
  - Cosi Fan Tutte: Publicity 1977-1978 (Box-folder 10.16)
  - Culpeper Community Concert 1977 (Box-folder 10.17)
  - Docent Program 1977 (Box-folder 10.18)
  - Dogwood Dell 1974 (Box-folder 11.1)
  - Dogwood Dell Concert 1976 (Box-folder 11.2)
  - Dogwood Dell Concert 1977 (Box-folder 11.3)
  - Dogwood Dell Concert and June Jubilee 1978 (Box-folder 11.4)
  - Dogwood Dell Concert 1979 (Box-folder 11.5)
  - Dogwood Dell Concert 1980-1981 (Box-folder 11.6)
  - Empire Theatre 1977-1979 (Box-folder 11.7)
  - Empire Theatre: Grand Opening 1977 (Box-folder 11.8)
  - Ensemble Concerts 1973 (Box-folder 11.9)
  - Ensemble Concerts 1976-1977 (Box-folder 11.10)
  - Ensemble Concerts 1977-1978 (Box-folder 11.11)
  - Ensemble Requests 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11.12)
  - Eskimo Pie Concert: Bob McGrath 1979 (Box-folder 12.1)
  - Eskimo Pie Spring Family Concert 1979 (Box-folder 12.2)
  - Fall Concerts 1980-1981 (Box-folder 12.2a)
  - First and Merchants Bank Concert 1979 (Box-folder 12.3)
  - Fort Lee Concert 1975 (Box-folder 12.4)
  - Gershwin Concert 1974 (Box-folder 12.5)
  - Goochland Festival 1975 (Box-folder 12.6)
  - Grand Lodge Concert: Ethel Merman/Eric Knight 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12.7)
  - Greene Memorial Church Concert 1976-1977 (Box-folder 12.8)
  - Hampden Sydney: Brass Quintet 1978 (Box-folder 12.9)
  - Harrisonburg Requiem 1982 (Box-folder 12.10)
  - Hartford Ballet 1978-1979 (Box-folder 12.11)
  - Henrico County School Concerts 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12.12)
  - Henrico County School Concerts 1975-1976 (Box-folder 12.13)
  - Henrico County School Concerts 1976-1977 (Box-folder 12.14)
  - Henrico County School Concerts 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12.15)
  - Heritage Savings and Loan: Reed Trio 1978 (Box-folder 12.16)
  - Inauguration Concert 1977-1978 (Box-folder 12.17)
  - Jaycees Concert 1974-1975 (Box-folder 12.18)
  - June Jubilee 1976 (Box-folder 12.19)
  - June Jubilee 1977 (Box-folder 12.20)
  - June Jubilee 1978 (Box-folder 12.21)
  - June Jubilee 1980 (Box-folder 12.22)
  - June Jubilee 1981 (Box-folder 12.23)
  - Kennedy Center 1975 (Box-folder 12.24)
  - Kings Dominion 1977 (Box-folder 12.25)
  - La Boheme 1979 (Box-folder 12.26)
  - Lollipop Concert 1974 (Box-folder 13.1)
  - Lollipop Concert 1975 (Box-folder 13.2)
  - Lollipop Concert 1976 (Box-folder 13.3)
  - Lollipop Concert: Bob McGrath 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13.4)
  - Lollipop Concert: Bob McGrath 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13.5)
  - Lynchburg College Concert 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13.6)
  - Lynchburg Community Concert 1976-1977 (Box-folder 13.7)
  - Madison College 1975 (Box-folder 13.8)
  - Matinee Concert: Richmond Symphony Chorus 1973 (Box-folder 13.9)
  - The Messiah: James Erb, Conductor 1979 (Box-folder 13.10)
  - Miscellaneous Concert Productions 1975-1976 (Box-folder 13.11)
  - The Nutcracker 1976 (Box-folder 13.12)
  - The Nutcracker 1977 (Box-folder 13.13)
  - The Nutcracker 1978 (Box-folder 13.14)
  - The Nutcracker 1979 (Box-folder 13.15)
  - The Nutcracker 1980 (Box-folder 13.16)
  - Opera Gala 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13.17)
  - Opera Gala: Artists Backgrounds 1975 (Box-folder 13.18)
  - Orchestra Showcase 1980 (Box-folder 13.19)
  - Performing Halls 1979-1980 (Box-folder 13.20)
  - Petersburg Nostalgiafest Concert 1977 (Box-folder 13.21)
  - Phillip Morris: Brass Quintet 1978 (Box-folder 13.22)
  - Pittsylvania County School Concert 1975 (Box-folder 13.23)
  - Pops Concert 1974 (Box-folder 13.24)
  - Pops: Doc Severinsen 1977-1978 (Box-folder 13.25)
  - Pops: Emporia, Va. with the Lettermen 1983 (Box-folder 13.26)
  - Pops: Occasion for the Arts, Williamsburg, Va 1982 (Box-folder 13.27)
  - Randolph Macon Concert 1976 (Box-folder 14.1)
  - Randolph Macon Concerts 1978 (Box-folder 14.2)
  - Randolph Macon Concerts: Marks, Vaught and Luca 1977-1978 (Box-folder 14.3)
  - Rappahannock Music Study Club 1976 (Box-folder 14.4)
  - Rappahannock Music Study Club 1978 (Box-folder 14.5)
  - Reed Trio: Abingdon, Va 1983 (Box-folder 14.6)
  - Reed Trio: Ash Lawn, Charlottesville, Va 1983 (Box-folder 14.7)
  - Regency Square: Salute the Sinfonia 1975 (Box-folder 14.6)
  - Regency Square Concert 1976 (Box-folder 14.7)
  - Richmond Ballet Concert 1978 (Box-folder 14.8)
  - Richmond Ballet Concert 1980 (Box-folder 14.9)
  - Richmond Ballet: Concerto do Aranjuez 1979 (Box-folder 14.10)
  - Richmond Craft Fair: Brass Duo 1978 (Box-folder 14.11)
  - Richmond Friends of Opera/Home Benefit 1981 (Box-folder 14.12)
  - Richmond Friends of Opera/V.O.A: Porgy and Bess 1980 (Box-folder 14.13)
  - Richmond Jaycees: Woodwind Quintet 1976 (Box-folder 14.14)
  - St. John's Church 1977 (Box-folder 14.15)
  - Scottish Rite Temple 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.16)
  - Shenandoah Valley Music Festival 1979 (Box-folder 14.17)
  - Sinfonia Contacts 1974 (Box-folder 14.18)
  - Sinfonia: In-School Concerts, General 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14.19)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.20)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.21)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.22)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1973-1974 (Box-folder 14.23)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.1)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.2)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.3)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.4)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15.5)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs and Specials 1978-1979 (Box-folder 15.6)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs and Specials 1978-1979 (Box-folder 15.7)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs Ferrum/Va. Intermont 1980 (Box-folder 15.8)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out (Randolph Macon) 1980 (Box-folder 15.9)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs, Fall 1982 (Box-folder 15.10)
  - Sinfonia Run-Outs 1982-1983 (Box-folder 15.11)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Aylett Country School Day 1983 (Box-folder 15.12)
  - Sinfonia Run-Out: Dido and Aneas, Winchester/Leesburg, Va 1983 (Box-folder 15.13)